Earth’s deadliest soldiers just became the galaxy’s last hope.
Osiris is a science fiction, action, horror film directed by William Kaufman.
Special Forces commandos on a mission are abducted
mid-operation by a mysterious spacecraft.
Upon waking aboard, they find themselves prey to a
relentless alien race in a fight for survival.
Kelly, played by Max Martini.
Ravi, played by Brianna Hildebrand.
Rhodie, played by LaMonica Garrett.
Reyes, played by Michael Irby.
Anya, played by Linda Hamilton.
Scars, played by Stanley White Jr..
Osiris is a 2025 American science fiction action film
written and directed by William Kaufman.
It stars Max Martini, Brianna Hildebrand, LaMonica
Garrett, Michael Irby and Linda Hamilton.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.